[
    {
      "question": "the work done by a social woeker ",
      "choice1": "caseworker",
      "choice2": "paddled",
      "choice3": "glum",
      "choice4": "suspicion",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "To hit someone with a paddle as a punishment ",
      "choice1": "caseworker",
      "choice2": "paddled",
      "choice3": "glum",
      "choice4": "suspicion",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "unhappy",
      "choice1": "caseworker",
      "choice2": "paddled",
      "choice3": "glum",
      "choice4": "suspicion",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "A feeling or thought that something bad is likely or true",
      "choice1": "caseworker",
      "choice2": "paddled",
      "choice3": "glum",
      "choice4": "suspicion",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "to provide the care that a parent usually gives to a child",
      "choice1": "foster",
      "choice2": "commence",
      "choice3": "provoked",
      "choice4": "Urchins",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "To begin, start",
      "choice1": "foster",
      "choice2": "commence",
      "choice3": "provoked",
      "choice4": "Urchins",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "to cause someone to become angry",
      "choice1": "foster",
      "choice2": "commence",
      "choice3": "provoked",
      "choice4": "Urchins",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "A mischievous{ a troublemaker} young child A small sea animal thay lives on the ocean floor",
      "choice1": "foster",
      "choice2": "commence",
      "choice3": "provoked",
      "choice4": "Urchins",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "A sort or kind ",
      "choice1": "ilk",
      "choice2": "conscience",
      "choice3": "spigots",
      "choice4": "lam",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "An inner feeling or voice that acts as a guide to one to make right or wrong choices.",
      "choice1": "ilk",
      "choice2": "conscience",
      "choice3": "spigots",
      "choice4": "lam",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Faucets on a sink",
      "choice1": "ilk",
      "choice2": "conscience",
      "choice3": "spigots",
      "choice4": "lam",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Escaping or trying to avoid being caught by the police.",
      "choice1": "ilk",
      "choice2": "conscience",
      "choice3": "spigots",
      "choice4": "lam",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Not in good condition; shabby",
      "choice1": "raggedy",
      "choice2": "sag",
      "choice3": "tetters",
      "choice4": "lam",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Hang down in the middle especially because of weight or weakness",
      "choice1": "raggedy",
      "choice2": "sag",
      "choice3": "tetters",
      "choice4": "lam",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Skin disease in humans or animals causing itchy patches, such as eczema or ringworm",
      "choice1": "raggedy",
      "choice2": "sag",
      "choice3": "tetters",
      "choice4": "lam",
      "answer": 3
    }
]

